Brokerage is bullish on ICC Lombard shares. There is a
great opportunity to earn 16% profit. Motilal Oswal has given a
research report rating to ICC Lombard. The
brokerage has set a target price of Rs 1550 for this stock in one year. According to
this, the stock has the
potential to rise by more than 16% from the current price.
Stock Market: If you are
looking for a good stock to invest in, you
can keep an eye on the shares of Insurance Company Insurance Company.
Actually, the brokerage firm is keeping a close eye on this stock.
Motilal Oswal has
given a research report rating to ICC Lombard. The
brokerage has set a target price of Rs 1550 for this stock in one year. The price has closed at Rs 13296. This is the brokerage firm's view. Motilal Oswal has given a research report rating to ICC Lombard. The brokerage has set a target price of Rs 1550 for this stock in one year. The price has
closed at Rs 13296.
This is the
research report of the brokerage firm.
Indian Insurance The Indian insurance
industry is flourishing and is
ready for the general insurance industry with the new reforms and initiatives introduced by ICC.
In its annual report, ICC reiterated its future preparedness for this fast-
growing general insurance industry.  The
brokerage further said that the company's business
strategy is based on five possibilities: one - increasing
market share; two - enhancing customer service and
technology; three - capturing new market share; three -
strengthening risk management;
and five - improving operational profitability. The
brokerage further said that the
company's
flagship products ICC Lombard
Complete Health Insurance and Health
Advantage have been revamped to attract the healthcare segment.
ICC Lombard's shares have seen a
good growth of 12% in the last one month,
while in the last six months it has given a return of Rs.
18% in the last one year. In the
last five years, it has generated a profit of 85% on its investments.